{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 18x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1/4, -2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*8*4}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*8*4}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{196}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{196}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 6x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-3 + √(3))/2, (-3 -  √(3))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 6, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{6*6 - 4*2*3}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{6*6 - 4*2*3}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{12}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{12}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 14x + 49 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-7", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 49\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*1*49}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*1*49}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{0}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{0}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 14x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-7 + √(47), -7 - √(47)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*1*2}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*1*2}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{188}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{188}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 18x + 7 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-9 + √(74), -9 - √(74)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 7\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*1*7}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*1*7}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{296}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{296}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 10x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-5 + √(21), -5 - √(21)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{10*10 - 4*1*4}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{10*10 - 4*1*4}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{84}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{84}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 12x + 11 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1, -11", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 11\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-12 + √{12*12 - 4*1*11}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-12 - √{12*12 - 4*1*11}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-12 + √{100}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-12 - √{100}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 19x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(341))/2, (-19 -  √(341))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*1*5}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*1*5}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{341}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{341}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 15x + 6 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(33))/16, (-15 -  √(33))/16", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 6\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*8*6}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*8*6}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{33}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{33}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 11x + 11 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-11 + √(33))/4, (-11 -  √(33))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 11\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{11*11 - 4*2*11}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{11*11 - 4*2*11}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{33}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{33}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 15x + 8 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(97))/8, (-15 -  √(97))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 8\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*4*8}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*4*8}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{97}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{97}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 19x + 17 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1, -17/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 17\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*2*17}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*2*17}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{225}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{225}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 14x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-7 + √(41))/4, (-7 -  √(41))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*4*2}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*4*2}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{164}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{164}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 11x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-11 + √(61))/6, (-11 -  √(61))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{11*11 - 4*3*5}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{11*11 - 4*3*5}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{61}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{61}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 19x + 45 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-9/2, -5", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 45\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*2*45}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*2*45}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{1}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{1}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 8x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-2 + √(2), -2 - √(2)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 8, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{8*8 - 4*2*4}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{8*8 - 4*2*4}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{32}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{32}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 18x + 25 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-9 + 2√(14), -9 - 2√(14)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 25\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*1*25}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*1*25}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{224}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{224}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(6x^2 + 11x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1/3, -3/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 6, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{11*11 - 4*6*3}}/{2*6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{11*11 - 4*6*3}}/{2*6}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{49}}/{12}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{49}}/{12}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 18x + 9 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-9 + 6√(2), -9 - 6√(2)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 9\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*1*9}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*1*9}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{288}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{288}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 17x + 15 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1, -15/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 15\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*2*15}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*2*15}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{169}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{169}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 18x + 9 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + 3√(5))/4, (-9-3√(5))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 9\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*4*9}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*4*9}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{180}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{180}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 17x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + √(129))/16, (-17 -  √(129))/16", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*8*5}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*8*5}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{129}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{129}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 18x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(79))/2, (-9 -  √(79))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*2*1}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*2*1}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{316}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{316}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 19x + 11 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(185))/8, (-19 -  √(185))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 11\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*4*11}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*4*11}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{185}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{185}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 16x + 13 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1, -13/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 13\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{16*16 - 4*3*13}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{16*16 - 4*3*13}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{100}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{100}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 13x + 6 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-13 + √(97))/6, (-13 -  √(97))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 13, c \u003d 6\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{13*13 - 4*3*6}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{13*13 - 4*3*6}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{97}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{97}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 12x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-6 + √(33))/3, (-6 -  √(33))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-12 + √{12*12 - 4*3*1}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-12 - √{12*12 - 4*3*1}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-12 + √{132}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-12 - √{132}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 15x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(193))/4, (-15 -  √(193))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*2*4}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*2*4}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{193}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{193}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 15x + 8 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(97))/8, (-15 -  √(97))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 8\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*4*8}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*4*8}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{97}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{97}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 19x + 38 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(209))/2, (-19 -  √(209))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 38\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*1*38}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*1*38}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{209}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{209}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 15x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(185))/10, (-15 -  √(185))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*5*2}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*5*2}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{185}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{185}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 13x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-13 + √(137))/16, (-13 -  √(137))/16", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 13, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{13*13 - 4*8*1}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{13*13 - 4*8*1}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{137}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{137}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 19x + 27 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(145))/4, (-19 -  √(145))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 27\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*2*27}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*2*27}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{145}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{145}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 18x + 38 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(5))/2, (-9 -  √(5))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 38\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*2*38}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*2*38}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{20}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{20}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 17x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + √(249))/10, (-17 -  √(249))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*5*2}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*5*2}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{249}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{249}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 10x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-5 + √(19))/3, (-5 -  √(19))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{10*10 - 4*3*2}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{10*10 - 4*3*2}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{76}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{76}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 13x + 13 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-13 + 3√(13))/2, (-13-3√(13))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 13, c \u003d 13\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{13*13 - 4*1*13}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{13*13 - 4*1*13}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{117}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{117}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 11x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-11 + √(41))/8, (-11 -  √(41))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{11*11 - 4*4*5}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{11*11 - 4*4*5}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{41}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{41}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 17x + 40 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + √(129))/2, (-17 -  √(129))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 40\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*1*40}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*1*40}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{129}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{129}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 11x + 6 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-3/4, -2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 6\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{11*11 - 4*4*6}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{11*11 - 4*4*6}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{25}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{25}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 18x + 7 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(46))/5, (-9 -  √(46))/5", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 7\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*5*7}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*5*7}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{184}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{184}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 10x + 22 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-5 + √(3), -5 - √(3)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 22\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{10*10 - 4*1*22}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{10*10 - 4*1*22}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{12}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{12}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 18x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + 2√(14))/5, (-9-2√(14))/5", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*5*5}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*5*5}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{224}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{224}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(6x^2 + 16x + 6 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-4 + √(7))/3, (-4 -  √(7))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 6, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 6\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{16*16 - 4*6*6}}/{2*6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{16*16 - 4*6*6}}/{2*6}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{112}}/{12}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{112}}/{12}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 20x + 14 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-5 + √(11))/2, (-5 -  √(11))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 14\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-20 + √{20*20 - 4*4*14}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-20 - √{20*20 - 4*4*14}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-20 + √{176}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-20 - √{176}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 17x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + 3√(21))/10, (-17-3√(21))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*5*5}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*5*5}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{189}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{189}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(7x^2 + 19x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(221))/14, (-19 -  √(221))/14", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 7, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*7*5}}/{2*7}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*7*5}}/{2*7}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{221}}/{14}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{221}}/{14}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 9x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(33))/6, (-9 -  √(33))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 9, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{9*9 - 4*3*4}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{9*9 - 4*3*4}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{33}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{33}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 18x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(41))/8, (-9 -  √(41))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*8*5}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*8*5}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{164}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{164}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 14x + 6 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-3/4, -1", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 6\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*8*6}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*8*6}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{4}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{4}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 4x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 4, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-4 + √{4*4 - 4*4*1}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-4 - √{4*4 - 4*4*1}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-4 + √{0}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-4 - √{0}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 16x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-8 + 2√(11))/5, (-8-2√(11))/5", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{16*16 - 4*5*4}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{16*16 - 4*5*4}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{176}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{176}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 18x + 7 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(53))/4, (-9 -  √(53))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 7\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*4*7}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*4*7}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{212}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{212}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 19x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(357))/2, (-19 -  √(357))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*1*1}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*1*1}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{357}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{357}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 12x + 35 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-5, -7", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 35\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-12 + √{12*12 - 4*1*35}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-12 - √{12*12 - 4*1*35}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-12 + √{4}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-12 - √{4}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 15x + 30 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(105))/2, (-15 -  √(105))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 30\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*1*30}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*1*30}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{105}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{105}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 15x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(145))/10, (-15 -  √(145))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*5*4}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*5*4}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{145}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{145}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 19x + 7 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(305))/4, (-19 -  √(305))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 7\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*2*7}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*2*7}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{305}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{305}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 20x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-5 + √(19))/4, (-5 -  √(19))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-20 + √{20*20 - 4*8*3}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-20 - √{20*20 - 4*8*3}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-20 + √{304}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-20 - √{304}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 20x + 12 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-2/3, -6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 12\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-20 + √{20*20 - 4*3*12}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-20 - √{20*20 - 4*3*12}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-20 + √{256}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-20 - √{256}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 19x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(321))/4, (-19 -  √(321))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*2*5}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*2*5}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{321}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{321}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 8x + 13 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-4 + √(3), -4 - √(3)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 8, c \u003d 13\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{8*8 - 4*1*13}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{8*8 - 4*1*13}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{12}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{12}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 16x + 17 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-8 + √(13))/3, (-8 -  √(13))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 17\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{16*16 - 4*3*17}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{16*16 - 4*3*17}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{52}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{52}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 7x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-3/4, -1", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 7, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-7 + √{7*7 - 4*4*3}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-7 - √{7*7 - 4*4*3}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-7 + √{1}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-7 - √{1}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 18x + 9 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-9 + 6√(2), -9 - 6√(2)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 9\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*1*9}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*1*9}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{288}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{288}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 18x + 38 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(5))/2, (-9 -  √(5))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 38\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*2*38}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*2*38}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{20}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{20}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 16x + 8 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-8 + 2√(14), -8 - 2√(14)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 8\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{16*16 - 4*1*8}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{16*16 - 4*1*8}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{224}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{224}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 17x + 15 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + √(229))/2, (-17 -  √(229))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 15\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*1*15}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*1*15}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{229}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{229}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(7x^2 + 14x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-7 + √(14))/7, (-7 -  √(14))/7", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 7, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*7*5}}/{2*7}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*7*5}}/{2*7}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{56}}/{14}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{56}}/{14}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 6x + 5 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1, -5", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 6, c \u003d 5\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{6*6 - 4*1*5}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{6*6 - 4*1*5}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{16}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{16}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 16x + 33 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-8 + √(31), -8 - √(31)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 33\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{16*16 - 4*1*33}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{16*16 - 4*1*33}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{124}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{124}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 18x + 8 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(57))/3, (-9 -  √(57))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 8\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*3*8}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*3*8}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{228}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{228}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 16x + 45 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-8 + √(19), -8 - √(19)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 45\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{16*16 - 4*1*45}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{16*16 - 4*1*45}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-16 + √{76}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-16 - √{76}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 17x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + √(253))/6, (-17 -  √(253))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*3*3}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*3*3}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{253}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{253}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 11x + 12 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-11 + √(73))/2, (-11 -  √(73))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 12\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{11*11 - 4*1*12}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{11*11 - 4*1*12}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{73}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{73}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 15x + 25 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + 5√(5))/2, (-15-5√(5))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 25\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*1*25}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*1*25}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{125}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{125}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 19x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(353))/4, (-19 -  √(353))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*2*1}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*2*1}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{353}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{353}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 5x + 6 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 5, c \u003d 6\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-5 + √{5*5 - 4*1*6}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-5 - √{5*5 - 4*1*6}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-5 + √{1}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-5 - √{1}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 18x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-9 + 4√(5), -9 - 4√(5)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*1*1}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*1*1}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{320}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{320}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 14x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-7 + √(43))/3, (-7 -  √(43))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*3*2}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*3*2}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{172}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{172}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 13x + 19 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-13 + √(17))/4, (-13 -  √(17))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 13, c \u003d 19\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{13*13 - 4*2*19}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{13*13 - 4*2*19}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-13 + √{17}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-13 - √{17}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 11x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-11 + 3√(13))/2, (-11-3√(13))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{11*11 - 4*1*1}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{11*11 - 4*1*1}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-11 + √{117}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-11 - √{117}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 7x + 11 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-7 + √(5))/2, (-7 -  √(5))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 7, c \u003d 11\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-7 + √{7*7 - 4*1*11}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-7 - √{7*7 - 4*1*11}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-7 + √{5}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-7 - √{5}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 14x + 7 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-7 + 2√(7))/3, (-7-2√(7))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 7\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*3*7}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*3*7}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{112}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{112}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 15x + 8 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(65))/10, (-15 -  √(65))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 8\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*5*8}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*5*8}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{65}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{65}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 6x + 4 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 6, c \u003d 4\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{6*6 - 4*2*4}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{6*6 - 4*2*4}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{4}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{4}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 9x + 17 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(13))/2, (-9 -  √(13))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 9, c \u003d 17\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{9*9 - 4*1*17}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{9*9 - 4*1*17}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{13}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{13}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(6x^2 + 14x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-7 + √(37))/6, (-7 -  √(37))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 6, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{14*14 - 4*6*2}}/{2*6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{14*14 - 4*6*2}}/{2*6}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-14 + √{148}}/{12}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-14 - √{148}}/{12}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(5x^2 + 19x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-19 + √(321))/10, (-19 -  √(321))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 5, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{19*19 - 4*5*2}}/{2*5}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{19*19 - 4*5*2}}/{2*5}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-19 + √{321}}/{10}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-19 - √{321}}/{10}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 15x + 49 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-15 + √(29))/2, (-15 -  √(29))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 49\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*1*49}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*1*49}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{29}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{29}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 17x + 15 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + √(109))/6, (-17 -  √(109))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 15\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*3*15}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*3*15}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{109}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{109}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 10x + 6 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-1, -3/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 6\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{10*10 - 4*4*6}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{10*10 - 4*4*6}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-10 + √{4}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-10 - √{4}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(x^2 + 17x + 11 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-17 + 7√(5))/2, (-17-7√(5))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 1, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 11\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{17*17 - 4*1*11}}/{2*1}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{17*17 - 4*1*11}}/{2*1}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-17 + √{245}}/{2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-17 - √{245}}/{2}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 9x + 9 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "-3/2, -3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 9, c \u003d 9\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{9*9 - 4*2*9}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{9*9 - 4*2*9}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{9}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{9}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(4x^2 + 9x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-9 + √(33))/8, (-9 -  √(33))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 4, b \u003d 9, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{9*9 - 4*4*3}}/{2*4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{9*9 - 4*4*3}}/{2*4}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-9 + √{33}}/{8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-9 - √{33}}/{8}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(8x^2 + 8x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-2 + √(2))/4, (-2 -  √(2))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 8, b \u003d 8, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{8*8 - 4*8*1}}/{2*8}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{8*8 - 4*8*1}}/{2*8}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{32}}/{16}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{32}}/{16}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(2x^2 + 6x + 1 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-3 + √(7))/2, (-3 -  √(7))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 2, b \u003d 6, c \u003d 1\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{6*6 - 4*2*1}}/{2*2}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{6*6 - 4*2*1}}/{2*2}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-6 + √{28}}/{4}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-6 - √{28}}/{4}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(6x^2 + 18x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-3 + √(7))/2, (-3 -  √(7))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 6, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{18*18 - 4*6*3}}/{2*6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{18*18 - 4*6*3}}/{2*6}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-18 + √{252}}/{12}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-18 - √{252}}/{12}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 8x + 2 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-4 + √(10))/3, (-4 -  √(10))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 8, c \u003d 2\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{8*8 - 4*3*2}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{8*8 - 4*3*2}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-8 + √{40}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-8 - √{40}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n\\(3x^2 + 15x + 3 \u003d 0\\)", "answer": "(-5 + √(21))/2, (-5 -  √(21))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\n\\(a \u003d 3, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 3\\)\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{15*15 - 4*3*3}}/{2*3}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{15*15 - 4*3*3}}/{2*3}\\)\nSimplify\n\\(x \u003d {-15 + √{189}}/{6}\\) or \\(x \u003d {-15 - √{189}}/{6}\\)", "prompt": "x \u003d"}
]}